Your search is the subject. Google or Twitter give the most relevant, or most recent
twitter_search = "road + closure"

[Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('A127', 'NNP')]),
 Tree('GPE', [('Southend', 'NNP')]),
 Tree('GPE', [('Southend', 'NNP')]),
 Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('A127', 'NNP')]),
 Tree('PERSON', [('Essex', 'NNP')])]

[[('on', 'IN')],
 [('in', 'IN')],
 [('in', 'IN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('out', 'IN'), ('of', 'IN')],
 [('on', 'IN')],
 [('on', 'IN')]]


Triple stores pass to Neo4j via gremlin queries
"road + closure" [('on', 'IN')], Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('A127', 'NNP')])
"road + closure"  ('in', 'IN')], Tree('GPE',  [('Southend', 'NNP')]),
"road + closure" [('in', 'IN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('out', 'IN'), ('of', 'IN')], Tree('GPE', [('Southend', 'NNP')]),
"road + closure"   [('on', 'IN')] Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('A127', 'NNP')])
"road + closure"   [('on', 'IN')] Tree('PERSON', [('Essex', 'NNP')])]